## ANGELA MCDANIEL

1330 Old Spanish Trl Houston, Texas 77054 Cell: 832-581-0253

E-Mail: 22amack@gmail.com

## Career Focus

Savvy Inside Marketing Representative with over eight years' experience in Marketing development for products and services towards increased revenues and success.

Telemarketing / Appointment Setting with more than, four years of experience planning, developing and generating sales through products marketing

## Summary of Skills

Client acquisition
Top-rated sales performance
Negotiation skills
Needs assessments
Online marketing strategies

## Accomplishments

Sales and Marketing
Increased annual gross sales
Worked with direct mass me

Worked with direct mass mailings which resulted in 8% growth of customer base.

Marketing Requirements

Assisted with marketing requirements documents for future product development.

Professional Experience

July 2015 to Present

Drive With Pride Car Dealership Houston Texas, Business Development Center Associate

Focused on increasing the sales traffic of dealership by receiving high volume inbound sales calls and making high volume outbounds calls - 150 plus calls a day .Using Vinsolutions & Xen software , Lead brokers Contact one and Client Connect

1

January 2011 to June 2015 Interactive of College Technology Houston, Texas Marketing Representative

Generated traffic to increase enrollment of students for an Computer and English second Language courses via by phone, email and participating in trade shows.

Created and executed marketing/PR campaigns, including new product introductions and existing product development.

Worked with cross functional resources to implement direct marketing programs, Communicated with customers, and other individuals to answer questions and explained product information.

March 2008 to December 2011 IMG Investment Houston Texas Marketing Manager

Outbound / Inbound Campaign Projects for Health insurance, Allstate, Forester, Central United Life, as well as Resorts and Timeshare.

Created scripts and reports for Call Center Campaign

Education

University Southern California Business Marketing

Coursework in Professional Prospecting Skills

References Upon Request